{
    "subject": "Amalie_Auguste_of_Bavaria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "John_of_Saxony",
    "human_readable": "Amalie Auguste of Bavaria is married to John of Saxony.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887661337852478,
            "question": "Is John of Saxony married to Amalie Auguste of Bavaria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9759373664855957,
            "question": "Who is Amalie Auguste of Bavaria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9577528834342957,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Amalie Auguste of Bavaria and John of Saxony?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939260721206665,
            "question": "Identify the spouse of Amalie Auguste of Bavaria."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9284404516220093,
            "question": "To whom was Amalie Auguste of Bavaria wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9179362058639526,
            "question": "What is the name of Amalie Auguste of Bavaria's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9092201590538025,
            "question": "What was the name of Amalie Auguste of Bavaria's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.887434720993042,
            "question": "Who is John of Saxony married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612055778503418,
            "question": "Name the wife of John of Saxony."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6709919571876526,
            "question": "Is Amalie Auguste of Bavaria a queen?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Amalie Auguste of Bavaria is married to John of Saxony.",
            "html": "yago_26126_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the wife of John of Saxony.",
            "html": "yago_26126_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is John of Saxony married to?",
            "html": "yago_26126_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Amalie Auguste of Bavaria's husband?",
            "html": "yago_26126_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26126_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the statement \"Amalie Auguste of Bavaria is married to John of Saxony\" is supported by the context information. This can be verified from multiple sources, including:\n\n- `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26126/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt`: It is mentioned that \"Amalie Auguste married on 22 November 1822 Prince John of Saxony...\"\n\n- `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26126/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt`: It is stated that \"Amalie married on November 22 1822 Prince John of Saxony, who became King of Saxony between 1854 and 1873.\"\n\n- `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26126/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt`: It is mentioned that \"Amalie Auguste married King John of Saxony.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Amalie Auguste of Bavaria's marriage to Prince John of Saxony, who later became the King of Saxony. This supports the statement that Amalie Auguste of Bavaria is married to John of Saxony."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}